babyworld.co.uk 2016-06-21

# Privacy & Security | Mode Media

**Mode Media Corporation  
Privacy and Security Policy**

Revised and posted as of December 27, 2014

Mode Media Corporation (“Mode Media”) owns and operates this website (the “Site”) and other websites focused on women, men, and social media consumers, (collectively the “Mode Media Sites”). Mode Media also operates an advertising network consisting of websites to which it may deliver advertising. That advertising network consists of the Mode Media Sites, and websites owned by third-party publishers displaying Mode Media branding and/or Mode Media logos (“Affiliated Sites”; together with the Mode Media Sites, the “Mode Media Network”). Mode Media may, from time to time, also deliver advertising to websites owned by third-party publishers that are not part of the Mode Media Network (“Non-Affiliated Sites”). This Privacy and Security Policy applies to (i) the collection of information on the Mode Media Sites that link to or display this Privacy and Security Policy and the use of that information, (ii) the collection of information on the Affiliated Sites and the use of that information when you view ads from our advertisers, and (iii) the collection of information on the Non-Affiliated Sites and the use of that information when you view ads from our advertisers.

**Privacy and Security Policy Overview**

This Privacy and Security Policy describes the kind of personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information collected on the Mode Media Sites linking to or displaying this Privacy and Security Policy and the non-personally identifiable information collected on the Affiliated Sites and Non-Affiliated Sites when you view advertisements from Mode Media advertisers, how the information collected is used and shared, and the choices you have regarding certain of these practices. This Privacy and Security Policy explains:

  * The Privacy and Security of Your Personal Information and Providing You with Choices Is Very Important to Mode Media
  * How Mode Media Collects Information about You
  * Use of Cookies, Log Files, Mode Adapt, and Other Technology
  * Information Collection on the Mode Media Sites
  * Website Usage
  * Online Transactions
  * Information Collection on Websites Participating in the Mode Media Network and on Non-Affiliated Sites
  * Transparency in Online Behavioral Advertising by Mode Media
  * Managing Your Privacy Choices
  * Updating Your Contact Preferences and Personal Information on Mode Media Sites
  * Your Choice to Opt Out: Mode Media Network and Non-Affiliated Sites
  * Using Public Areas of Mode Media Sites
  * What Else You Can Do About Your Privacy and Security
  * Other Things You Should Know
  * Our Security Practices
  * Our Data Sharing Practices
  * Our Data Retention Policy
  * This Privacy and Security Policy Applies to U.S. Customers
  * Our Privacy and Security Policy Will Change Over Time
  * Links to Third-Party Sites
  * Mode Media Sites Are Not for Use by Children
  * Mergers, Acquisitions, and Bankruptcy
  * Trademark Notice
  * Our Contact Information

**The Privacy and Security of Your Personal Information and Providing You with Choices Is Very Important to Mode Media**

Mode Media values our customers and guests and respects your concerns about online security and privacy. We believe in providing you with a safe and secure online experience. Our Privacy and Security Policy is intended to protect your privacy and ensure that your personal information is handled in a safe and responsible manner. By visiting, or registering for a Mode Media Site, you hereby accept the policies and practices described in this Privacy and Security Policy and agree and expressly consent to Mode Media’s collection, use, and disclosure of the information that you provide, or that is collected about you. In addition to reviewing this Privacy and Security Policy, you should also read our [Terms of Service](https://corp.mode.com/terms-of-service). Your use of any of the Mode Media Sites constitutes your agreement to its terms and conditions.

Mode Media is committed to responsible online advertising and as such is a member of the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) (“NAI”) and the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/) (“DAA”) and adheres to the NAI Code of Conduct and the Self Regulatory Principles of the DAA. As a member of the NAI and DAA, this Privacy and Security Policy provides you with notice of the types of information Mode Media may passively collect about you when you view a Mode Media advertisement on the Mode Media Network or a Non-Affiliated Site, and provides you with a choice to opt out of receiving future customized, targeted advertisements from Mode Media advertisers.

Please note that Mode Media is not responsible for and cannot control the privacy policies or privacy practices of the Mode Media Affiliated Sites and Non-Affiliated Sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies on these sites for the applicable privacy practices relating to personally identifiable information you may choose to provide in interacting with these websites and the non-personally identifiable information collected through the use of cookies and other technologies as they may differ from Mode Media’s privacy practices as set forth in this Privacy and Security Policy. Please further note that the opt out choice provided to you through this Privacy and Security Policy acts only to provide you with an opt out choice regarding customized, targeted advertisements from Mode Media and will have no effect on customized, targeted advertisements from third parties.

**How Mode Media Collects Information about You**

Mode Media collects information about you in three ways: (i) when you visit a Mode Media Site, Mode Media collects the information you voluntarily submit during your use of the site, and as you use the Mode Media Sites certain information may also be passively collected through the use of cookies and other technologies; (ii) when you visit a website participating in the Mode Media Network or a Non-Affiliated Site and view ads from our advertisers, Mode Media collects technical and usage information about your activities on the websites passively through use of cookies and other technologies; (iii) when third parties provide Mode Media with non-personally identifiable information.

**Use of Cookies, Log Files, Mode Adapt, and Other Technology**

Mode Media may use “cookies” on the websites participating in the Mode Media Network and Non-Affiliated Sites to collect or log certain information. A cookie is a small piece of information that a website stores on a personal computer and which it can later retrieve. The cookie identifier associated with your browser is the same cookie identifier used when you visit websites in the Mode Media Network and Non-Affiliated Sites. Mode Media owns and operates Mode Adapt, an online advertising product that may provide ad delivery and reporting across various websites, including the Mode Media Network and Non-Affiliated Sites. Mode Media may also use cookies for informational purposes, for example, to store our customers’ preferences for certain kinds of products or to serve advertisements tailored to a customer’s preferences. The cookies will not contain information that will enable anyone to contact our customers via telephone, e-mail, or any other means.  **If you are uncomfortable with the use of cookie technology, you may get more information on how toopt out of our cookies at any time by clicking here**. Please note, if you use more than one type of browser, or more than one computer to access the Internet, you will need to opt out in each browser and on each computer that you use. Certain types of Mode Media services, however, could be dependent on cookies, and you may disable those services by refusing cookies.

Third parties including advertising networks and advertisers may also serve ads throughout the Mode Media Network and Non-Affiliated Sites, and these third parties may also use their own cookies. Mode Media does not control these cookies or the data collection practices of these companies. For more information about these companies’ separate privacy policies, practices, and use of cookies, you should contact the advertising network directly. If the advertising network is a member of the NAI, you may be able to opt out of receiving targeted advertising delivered by NAI members by following the opt out directions on [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). If the advertising network is a member of the DAA, you may be able to opt out of receiving targeted advertising delivered by DAA members by following the opt out directions on [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

**Information Collection on the Mode Media Sites**

Mode Media may collect and maintain (or third parties with whom Mode Media has contracted, may collect and maintain on Mode Media’s behalf) information that you provide to us during your visit to a Mode Media Site. For example, you may provide information to the Site when you register, sign-in, search, participate in a test profile, survey or special offers, request our e-mail newsletters, or communicate with Mode Media’s customer service. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with information such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and personal shopping and product preferences. Mode Media uses information about you on the Mode Media Sites in several ways. Mode Media may use personally identifiable information (information including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to the Mode Media Sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you, or as more fully described below. We may share your personal information with third parties or affiliates of Mode Media with whom we have contracted to perform services on our behalf. All companies that act on our behalf are contractually obligated to keep the personal information we provide to them confidential and to use the personal information we share only to provide the services we ask them to perform. Please refer to the [Managing Your Privacy Choices](https://corp.mode.com/privacy/#_ManagingYourPrivacyChoices) section below for information on how to prevent or opt out of having certain types of information collected about you.

**Website Usage**

Mode Media or Mode Media’s authorized service providers may observe activities, preferences, and transactional data (such as your IP address, browser type, and operating system) relating to your use of Mode Media Sites. Mode Media may use this collected or logged information in order to provide better service, to facilitate our customers’ use of the websites, to track usage of the websites, and to address security hazards. Mode Media, or one of Mode Media’s authorized service providers, may also use this information to track aggregate traffic patterns. We may use aggregated, statistical information to describe our customer audience, products and services, and to develop partnerships with third parties to offer products and services in which we believe our customers will be interested.

**Online Transactions**

You may visit a Mode Media Site without registering, but if you enter a sweepstakes or contest, or use other special features that may be offered on our site, you may need to provide us with certain information such as your name, address, phone number, and e-mail address, to open an account with us. We may share your personal information with third parties or affiliates of Mode Media where it is necessary for us to complete a transaction or do something you have asked us to do. We may also use this information to assist you in creating a user ID and a password to protect your account information and facilitate your use of special features or to complete a transaction.

**Information Collection on Websites Participating in the Mode Media Network and on Non-Affiliated Sites**

When you visit any of the websites that participate in the Mode Media Network or a Non-Affiliated Site and view ads from Mode Media’s advertisers, Mode Media automatically receives and stores certain types of non-personally identifiable information including IP address, web pages viewed, date and time, and responses to advertisements delivered by Mode Adapt or third-party ad serving technologies. While each advertising technology uses different types of technology to collect this information, including log files, cookies and pixels, none of the foregoing by itself or together can be tracked to a specific individual’s personally identifiable information, and the non-personally identifiable information collected by Mode Media will not be shared with third parties, except as expressly indicated in this Privacy and Security Policy. The non-personally identifiable information collected through your use of the Mode Media Sites and the websites of the Mode Media Network, is used to provide relevant, targeted advertising and improve Mode Media’s advertising technology; monitor website traffic; collect statistical data; determine the effectiveness of advertisements and content; and collect data across multiple websites to categorize likely consumer interest segments for use in online behavioral advertising (“OBA”). Mode Media may track visits to the Mode Media Network and this information may be used over time to help predict your consumer interest segments and select the ad content you see. Mode Media may also use non-personally identifiable profile-based anonymous information with other non-personally identifiable information that Mode Media has obtained from Mode Adapt, third-party ad serving technologies, the Mode Media Network, and Non-Affiliated Sites. If you wish to opt out of receiving Mode Media’s customized targeted advertisements, you may opt out as indicated below at [Your Choice to Opt Out: Mode Media Network and Non-Affiliated Sites](https://corp.mode.com/privacy/#_YourChoicetoOptOut:ModeMediaNetworkandNon-AffiliatedSites).

**Transparency in Online Behavioral Advertising by Mode Media**

Online behavioral advertising (sometimes called “interest-based advertising” or “OBA”) uses information collected through your Web browser as you visit multiple websites in order to predict your preferences and show you relevant advertising. Mode Media does not create or use potentially sensitive data segments to provide its targeted online behavioral advertising for brand advertisers. However, we recognize that consumers may have differing opinions regarding which data segments are sensitive. In compliance with industry standards Mode Media provides transparency around health related audience segments collected and used by our technology solutions. We may use health related audience segments such as Health.CardioHealth, Wellness.DietNutrition, and Family.Pregnancy. For a full list of health related audience segments used click here.

**Managing Your Privacy Choices**  
****

**Updating Your Contact Preferences and Personal Information on Mode Media Sites**

You have choices when it comes to how Mode Media uses your personal information. When you register online with a Mode Media Site you can choose not to receive communications from us by e-mail. If you elect not to receive information by e-mail, Mode Media may continue to contact you as necessary to service your account. You can change your contact preferences at any time by following the instructions on the applicable Mode Media Site. Keeping your account information accurate and up-to-date is very important, so we can provide you with excellent service. If your account information is incomplete, inaccurate, or not current, please follow the instructions on the applicable Mode Media Site to correct your account information online. If you need additional assistance, please contact Mode Media customer service at [customercare @ modemediacorp.com](mailto:customercare@modemediacorp.com).

**Your Choice to Opt Out: Mode Media Network and Non-Affiliated Sites**

If you would like to opt out from receiving customized, targeted advertisements from Mode Media based upon non-personally identifiable information, you may get more information on how to opt out by clicking here. Opting out will not remove advertisements. You will continue to see advertisements provided by Mode Media, but the advertising will not be customized or targeted based on non-personally identifiable information collected by Mode Media. Please note that if you change computers or browsers, you will need to repeat this process for each computer and each browser.

**Using Public Areas of Mode Media Sites**

Any information disclosed in public areas of the Mode Media Sites, is public information that may be viewed and collected by any party. We cannot control the use of information disclosed in the social networking, chat rooms, reviews, or bulletin board portions of these Sites. You should exercise caution when disclosing information, including photos or images, in public areas of websites and should refrain from disclosing personally identifying information. If you wish to use some of the public portions on these Sites, we will direct you to first create a public ID, which is not your real e-mail address, before you can post information to our Site. Mode Media reserves the right to remove any information at any time from the Mode Media Sites that we deem inappropriate or for any other reason.

**What Else You Can Do About Your Privacy and Security**

You should be careful to maintain the secrecy of your passwords and/or account information and be responsible about protecting your personal information and identity whenever you are online.

**Other Things You Should Know**  
****

**Our Security Practices**

Our internal data security policies restrict access to customers’ personal information to authorized employees. Authorized employees may use our customers’ personal information for Mode Media business purposes only. Our employees are bound by Mode Media policies that require them to maintain the confidentiality of our customers’ personal information. Employees who violate these requirements are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination.  
We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that are designed to guard our customers’ personal information. For example, for the security of your online visit to a Mode Media Site, we may make use of firewall barriers, encryption techniques, and/or authentication procedures. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be absolutely secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Mode Media cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. In the event of a breach of the confidentiality or security of your personal information, we will notify you as necessary so you can take appropriate protective steps. Unless you indicate otherwise, we may notify you under such circumstances using the e-mail address you provided to us when you registered with the Mode Media Site.

**Our Data Sharing Practices**

**We do not sell your personally identifiable or non-personally identifiable information to third parties for any reason.  **We do not disclose your personally identifiable or non-personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties who may want to offer you their own products and services unless you have requested or authorized us to do so. We may share your personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information with third parties, or affiliates of Mode Media where it is necessary for us to complete a transaction or do something you have asked us to do. For example, we might need to provide your personally identifiable information to third parties, such as advertisers, featured on a Mode Media Site, or through a website participating in the Mode Media Network or a Non-Affiliated Site so they can process and fulfill your request for more information from them; and in these instances, we will provide you with a notice at the time of collection that the information is being shared, to whom it is being shared and the privacy policy governing the use of the information collected and shared. We may share your personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information with third parties with whom we have contracted to perform services on our behalf, or affiliates of Mode Media. All companies that act on our behalf are contractually obligated to keep the personal information we provide to them confidential and to use the personal information we share only to provide the services we ask them to perform.

We may disclose personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information about our customers as permitted or required by law, such as in connection with a subpoena or similar legal process, or in connection with a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy, as discussed further below.

**Our Data Retention Policy**

Mode Media is required to retain certain non–personally identifiable information collected from users of the Mode Media Sites, Affiliated Sites and Non-Affiliated Sites in order to provide audited information to advertisers and auditors. As a result, ad reporting and delivery data is retained for a period of 24 months. After 24 months, some of the ad reporting and delivery data may be aggregated for statistical purposes and retained indefinitely. Log files that associate individual advertising with a specific IP address will be retained by Mode Media for 24 months and during that time will be used for internal analysis and ad delivery purposes. Certain aggregated, non-personally identifiable information including historical data and attributes collected by Mode Media prior to an opt out election and which represent large numbers of users combined into aggregated statistical data and information shall be kept for 24 months and despite the fact that the user has opted out, the information will continue to be associated with the users cookie regardless of the opt out status. After 24 months some of the aggregated, non-personally identifiable information may be further aggregated for statistical purposes and retained indefinitely.

Additionally, Mode Media reserves the right to retain and use any information described in this Privacy and Security Policy as reasonably necessary to comply with all laws or regulations, regardless of any limitations set forth in this Policy. Mode Media reserves the right to change its data retention policy and the new data retention policy shall apply to all data collected following such change.

YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT MODE MEDIA’S LIABILITY REGARDING ANY DISPUTE OVER PRIVACY OR RELATED TO THIS PRIVACY AND SECURITY POLICY ARE HEREBY LIMITED AS SET FORTH IN THE MODE MEDIA SITES TERMS OF SERVICE.

**This Privacy and Security Policy Applies to U.S. Customers**

The Mode Media Sites are hosted in the United States and are intended for United States visitors. This Privacy and Security Policy applies to customer relationships established in the United States. Parts of this Privacy and Security Policy may not apply to visitors outside the United States. Like almost every website, the Mode Media Sites may be accessed by an international audience. If you are a non-U.S. visitor to any of the Mode Media Sites, by providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that your personal information may be processed for the purposes identified in this Privacy and Security Policy. In addition, such data may be stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction, which may have less stringent privacy practices than your own. By providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data.

**Our Privacy and Security Policy Will Change Over Time**

Because we continue to develop and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we provide, we reserve the right to change, or modify, any portion of this, or any other policy, from time to time without prior notice and any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless you are advised otherwise. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy and Security Policy from time to time to stay abreast of our most current privacy policy practices. If you are a registered member of a Mode Media Site, we may (but need not) notify you by e-mail of material changes to our Privacy and Security Policy using the most current e-mail address you have provided to us. Your continued access and use of a Mode Media Site constitutes your acceptance of any changes or revisions to our Privacy and Security Policy.

**Links to Third-Party Sites**

Mode Media Sites may contain links to third-party sites, which are maintained by third parties. Please be aware that Mode Media is not responsible for and cannot control the privacy policies of these other linked sites or their practices. We encourage you to read the privacy policies on these sites for applicable privacy practices relating to personally identifiable information you may choose to provide in interacting with these websites and the non-personally identifiable information collected through the use of cookies and other technologies collected via those sites because they may differ from Mode Media’s privacy practices.

**Mode Media Sites Are Not for Use by Children**  
Children are not eligible to use Mode Media Sites. We ask that minors (under the age of 18) only use Mode Media Sites in conjunction with your parents or guardians.

**Mergers, Acquisitions, and Bankruptcy**

If Mode Media should ever file for bankruptcy or merge with another company, or if Mode Media should decide to buy another business or sell or reorganize part or all of Mode Media’s business, Mode Media may be required to disclose both the information you provide to Mode Media and the information gathered by Mode Media to prospective or actual purchasers and other parties. It is Mode Media’s practice to obtain appropriate protections for information disclosed in these types of transactions. Mode Media cannot, however, guarantee that Mode Media’s Privacy and Security Policy will remain unchanged if Mode Media is sold or merges with another company.

**Trademark Notice**

Glam, Tend, and Brash are trademarks of Mode Media Corporation. Other featured words or symbols, used to identify the source of merchandise or services, may be the trademarks of their respective owners.

**Our Contact Information**

Mode Media Corporation  
2000 Sierra Point Parkway  
Suite 1000, 10th Floor  
Brisbane, CA 94005

If you have questions regarding your user account, our Privacy and Security Policy, your privacy choices, our Terms of Service, or any other topic, we are always happy to answer any questions or concerns you may have.

E-mail: [customercare@modemediacorp.com](mailto:customercare@modemediacorp.com)
